# Niklas Hansen

nha@3floor.dk (+45) 31 50 13 32

Started experimenting with (web) development during Primary School, and started working as freelancer in high school. I have since worked in a variety of different sectors, gaining valuable skills going forward. I am somewhat of a "techie" and I love implementing technology to help ease day-to-day work.

Twitter NinjafyDev GitHub NiklasHansen LinkedIn NiklasHansen

#### **SKILLS**

C#	.NET Framework, .NET Core, .NET 5, ASP.Net (Core), Entity Framework (Core)
GO	
RUST	Tokio
WEB DEVELOPMENT	HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, React, Angular
SQL	SQL Server, PostgreSQL, MySQL

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## Jyske Bank

Senior Software Developer Dec 2018 - Present

Jyske Bank is a Danish bank and mortgage credit company. I spent the first 5 years developing and maintaining systems regarding registration of real estate, property data and real estate valuation. I recently transitioned into a new position/team, focusing on customer self-service, app development and backend-for-frontend.

- Backend development
- Technical design and architecture
- Roadmap creation for systems
- Developing backend systems, and backend-for-frontends
- Creating services communicating with 3rd parties / external partners
- Tech stack: C#, TypeScript (Angular), Ionic, OpenShift (Kubernetes), SQL Server, IBM MQ

# Jyske Bank

Software Developer Nov 2016 - Nov 2018

## **Netcompany A/S**

Senior Architect Jan 2016 - Sep 2016

Netcompany is a Danish consultancy for both private sector and public sector customers. I worked in the ERP division, where I primarily worked with Microsoft Dynamics AX implementations.

- Implementing new Dynamics AX installations, and customizing for customer needs
- Developing integrations with 3rd party vendors and other products
- Tech stack: Dynamics AX, X++, C#, SQL Server

#### **Netcompany A/S**

**Developer** Aug 2014 - Dec 2015

#### Justfone A/S

**Developer** Sep 2013 - Aug 2014

Justfone was a start-up phone operator, with focus on building the entire system landscape from ground up, and giving customers more than they would get elsewhere. Justfone ended up being sold to TDC, and becoming Fullrate Erhverv.

- Backend development
- Implementation of letter fulfillment process generating letters, printing SIM-cards, and sending to printer
- Implementation of dunning flow and process
- Tech stack: C#, JavaScript, RavenDB, RabbitMQ, Amazon AWS (micro-service architecture), EventStore

#### Microsoft Development Center Copenhagen

Student Worker SDET Jul 2011 - Jun 2013

I was a student worker in ERP division of Microsoft, working on the Dynamics AX product.

Conversion of test cases using legacy framework in X++, to updated frameworks in C#.

#### **Relation Technology**

Web Developer Feb 2011 - May 2011

Relation Technology was a small Danish web consultancy, with a wide variety of customers.

- Development of websites and webshops for customers
- Maintenance of customer's website
- Development and maintenance of internal communication tool
- Tech stack: PHP, HTML, CSS, JavaScript (ExtJS), MySQL

#### Customerwise

Web Developer Mar 2009 - Feb 2011

Customerwise was a small Danish web consultancy, with a wide variety of customers.

- Developing websites for customers (both frontend and backend)
- Development of the company's CMS

■ Tech stack: PHP, HTML, CSS, JavaScript (jQuery), MySQL

### **VOLUNTEERING**

### StreetCup

Board member Dec 2012 - Dec 2014

StreetCup was an organization fighting for legal street racing in Denmark

#### **EDUCATION**

### **IT-University of Copenhagen**

Aug 2010 - Jun 2013 Bachelor - Software Development

# Erhvervsskolen Nordsjælland

Aug 2007 - Jun 2010 HTX - Math/IT

#### Lærkeskolen

Dec 1999 - Dec 2007 Municipal primary and lower secondary school

#### **LANGUAGES**

#### English

Fluent

#### Danish

Native speaker

### **INTERESTS**

Cars & motorsports

Gaming & e-sports